Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-
We secured the whole perimeter. It's okay.
What the hell?
I gave you 24 hours and now I have
three dead Albanian gangsters.
This is a fucking nightmare.
We've got to bring those women
in before they kill anyone else.
You don't know this was them!
What makes you think this wasn't them?
They get on a train. a man is dead.
They get to Castille.
four drug dealers end up in the hospital.
They get to Monaco.
three Albanians are dead in the street.
I'm putting out the Red Notice.
If you do that. we lose...
We have already lost any chance of
getting to Ergon Kreshnik.
We tried. we failed.
Your Veronica Gillingsby isn't
going to help us.
Her name's not even Veronica!
It's Debbie Claybourne.
She's the wife of a British MP.
It's a fake passport.
She's running. and she's scared.
How do you know?
Oh my god. you've met her.
So if you had her. how did she get away?
Did she hit you?
No. an Albanian hit me.
And then I got distracted because
the house caught on fire.
Enough! Stop. You're done.
It's over.
No Colette.
please just give me a little time.
I don't think you understand. actually.
You seem to be under the impression
this is couple's therapy.
This is not a discussion. that's an order.
You can go home now.
Call me when he wakes up.
Boss.
Look.
Get him! He's in that car!
Please keep this out of the press.
I don't want any information leaking out.
Understood.
Lieutenant!
Listen. I've approved it this time.
but if you're going
to take medical supplies
we really need you to fill out
the whole form. not just the first page.
That must be a mistake.
What are you talking about?
I didn't take out any medical supplies.
Your signature is right there.
Ah. exactly. must have forgotten.
won't happen again.
Lieutenant.
Son of a bitch.
We need to find Jacques.
It won't be complicated.
I put a tracker on his phone back when
I thought he was having an affair.
And was he? Having an affair?
No. I was.
The other one. where is she?
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org